♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
[Martina] We need to find someone
who can pretend
to be Ibyang's real mother.
[Ame] Atoy! She's Ibyang's mother!
[Olga] Where is she?
[Atoy] How can I be sure
you're really Ibyang's mother?
[Olga] Martin is my ex.
He's Ibyang's real father.
Are you really my mama?
[Olga] We'll be together now.
And if you'll agree, we'll go home.
I can't relax.
Oh. Why?
[Olga] Because of Atoy.
He's so suspicious of me!
[Atoy] You will request
a maternity match test.
And it's rush.
Okay.
This role is crucial.
[Olga] We'll go inside
that tailoring shop.
Then we'll pretend to be a wealthy couple.
You need to distract him. Okay? Clear?
[henchman] Clear, ma'am.
What about Brother Atoy?
[T-Bak] Then he'll go solo in life!
Positive, Emerson.
She really is the mother.
Hello, Atoy! I'll fetch Ibyang.
Where's Olga? Why--
Olga is at home, cleaning.
Preparing for Ibyang's arrival.
Will Ibyang take long?
- I'll just call her.
- Ah, okay.
PREVIOUSLY
♪ Fix this  ♪
Oh, I'll pass by Brother Atoy's.
Sis Ame said Ibyang is leaving today.
- I'll come too.
- Okay.
[chuckles] All right.
Ibyang!
- Ibyang!
- Baby girl!
- [in English] How are you?
- Hey!
You're leaving today, baby girl?
Yes.
I want to say goodbye to all of you.
Ibyang, always take care. Be a good girl.
[in English] Ibyang, when you come
visit us next time, free pares on me.
- Hmm? [chuckles softly]
- [Siony] Hey, quiet!
You're stealing the moment!
Child, we'll miss you.
I'll miss you too.
So much!
- Like ten million misses!
- Oh, that's a lot.
- That's too much.
- [chuckles]
[Nestor] That's a lot, huh.
[Emerson] Ibyang! Wait, wait.
Ibyang, don't be too naughty
at your mom. Okay?
Take care of yourself, Ibyang.
Study well. Don't be like me.
Yes, Sister Karla, Brother Emerson.
[Cita] Ibyang!
Oh? Miss Cita.
[melancholic music playing]
Where's Sister Ame?
Don't worry, she's with us
here in Tabang Lupa.
We won't abandon her.
And Tatoy too.
San Antonio de Padua!
Thank you that Ibyang
has found her mother.
And Lord, please guide
this good child every day.
Bless you, Ibyang.
[all] Amen!
Thank you.
- Take care, okay?
- I will.
- Take care, okay.
- Yes.
Yes. Bye-bye. Take care.
[inaudible]
[suave theme music playing]
Here, I'm giving you a cellphone.
It's yours now.
I want you to use it.
I want you to use it responsibly, okay?
No social media.
Social media is forbidden.
I'll put it in your bag. Okay?
I want you to call me.
You've memorized my number, right?
I memorized your number,
but I also saved mine there just in case.
- [in English] Okay?
- [in English] Okay.
[gentle music playing]
[in English] Take care.
Tell Olga to call me
- [Charmi] Ah, okay.
- if you need anything.
[Charmi] I'll tell her.
Ibyang, get inside!
[car door clicks shut]
[sentimental music playing]
[Ibyang] Someday,
you'll need me in your missions.
I don't need anyone to help me.
You'll swallow your words,
and you'll choke! [coughs]
[Ibyang] No one will bring you water,
except me!
Tatoy,
thank you for your love.
Every day, I feel it,
even if you're not my real father.
In my heart, you're the true hero.
Thank you for everything, Tatoy.
I love you, Tatoy!
I love you too, Ibyang.
My Tatoy.
[music fades]
[engines whirring]
Please stop, please!
Wait. Please stop, please!
[epic music playing]
Tatoy!
What are you still doing here?
[sobbing]
Your mother is waiting for you.
You need to go to her.
[sobbing]
Tatoy,
I just want to hug you again.
Don't neglect yourself, okay?
[sobbing]
Eat well.
Don't be grumpy with your customers, okay?
- [chuckles]
- [sobbing]
Always be happy.
So I won't worry about you.
[sobs]
You're not allowed to die
on your missions.
Yes, yes.
[sobbing]
Thank you, Tatoy.
If not for you,
I wouldn't have had a family.
- [sobbing]
- [sentimental music playing]
No one can replace you because I love you.
Thank you too.
Because you know, because of you…
When you came into my life…
I got to know myself better.
[Ibyang sobbing]
That's why I love you so much, Ibyang.
I'll miss you.
[sobbing]
You'll always… always be stitched…
right here in my heart.
- Okay?
- [sobbing]
Take care, okay? Take care.
Okay? Be good. Okay?
- [Atoy] Go now.
- [sobbing]
Go. Just keep me updated.
[in English] You look disappointed.
But I have something that's gonna
put a smile on your face.
[sinister music playing]
Olga has Ibyang now.
Good thing Atoy agreed.
Yes. But now that we have the kid,
what's your plan?
[suspicious music playing]
As long as we have Ibyang,
Atoy can't do anything against us.
The child is our trump card.
Hon, I get that.
But what?
The child will stay with Olga forever?
We'll raise Audrey's daughter?
Of course not.
So, what then?
Eventually, the child
has to be disposed of.
What do you mean, disposed of?
Ah, maybe included in a shipment or…
Get rid of her, so there's no trace.
[Martina scoffs]
[in English] Hon, she's just a child.
I don't want to be a part of that.
Who said you'd be the one to do it?
[in English] I'll do it.
[tense music playing]
Come in.
[sighs]
[Olga] Are you hungry?
There's still food in the fridge.
Go ahead and get some.
Ma, why did you put this in the fridge?
It's spoiled already.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Sorry.
[Olga] Better fix your things upstairs.
Hmm? I'll just go to the supermarket.
The mall nearby, the one you saw earlier.
Your room is upstairs.
- Okay.
- Wait.
You're leaving me here?
I'll be quick.
It won't take long, okay?
Hey!
Aren't you going to wait for your child?
She'll be fine.
[sneaky music playing]
Sister Olga, my project, okay?
It's almost due.
Relax. It's almost done. Just wait.
And don't forget the payment.
[in English] Okay?
[in English] Thank you!
[Olga chuckles softly]
She's hustling.
She's hustling, oh!
Oh, small-time hustle
like doing student projects,
and you already have money.
- Oh! Wait. Speaking of money.
- Mmm?
- Here she comes! Fifty K!
- Huh? Hmm!
She got money right away,
just pretending to be Faye.
[giggles]
Told you so.
Hey, have you thought about it?
Where could Ibyang's real mother be?
Now you're asking,
when you already have the money.
- Forget it.
- No.
Because what if Ibyang's real mother
is really looking for her?
So what? You feel guilty?
Then let's just return the money.
- Give it to me.
- No. No, no, hey, hey. I'm just curious.
Because the child is so kind.
She's easy to love, right?
Oh, now you must act like a full-time mom.
What about your dream
of being rich and famous?
Hmm.
Just wait. It'll come.
For now, this hustle will do, right?
This isn't forever.
What's important is I'm getting paid.
So, even if I have to act
like a single mom all day,
I can handle it.
Go!
Mmm.
- What?
- Oh!
You know what?
Your child should have a father too,
so it's a complete family!
Oh! Atoy could be a candidate.
- Eh!
- He's handsome,
Ibyang knows him, and--
- Oh. You have history! Ohh.
- [in English] Past is past.
And besides, I don't want
to share the money.
This racket is mine alone.
That's right.
You're right.
Okay, fine. I have to go.
I'll go now, okay?
Hey, wait. Aren't you coming
with me to the grocery store?
Oh.
No, you can handle it!
I'll just check out what's in my cart.
I already have money.
So arrogant!
- [giggles] Bye-bye!
- Okay then.
[somber music playing]
Miss!
- Psst. You're too noisy!
- [chuckles]
They might hear you. Is Atoy there?
Yes.
He's there. We're
just drowning his sadness.
He invited us.
[Emerson chuckles softly]
Don't leave him, okay?
Stay with him.
No.
Of course.
Well… Well, as long
as he pays for the drinks.
- Me, I'll just be the server.
- Hmm?
No, just kidding.
Come on, miss. You're too serious.
I'm just joking,
because that's what I do to him also.
I just joke with him,
so he'll smile a little,
despite what he's going through.
Will you talk to him?
Even if I want to,
I don't think he'll talk to me.
Hmm.
[somber music playing]
Oh.
Ah, fried dumpling,
with vinegar and sweet sauce.
You should buy that.
It's their favorite, his and Ibyang's.
- Take charge, okay?
- Yes, sir. Okay.
[Emerson chuckles softly]
[Olga] Ibyang!
Sorry. I got home late!
So many people at the groce--
[pensive music playing]
Is this my house?
Ma, let's eat.
I cooked.
[pensive music playing]
[Olga] You're unbelievable!
You opened the imported corned beef?!
[sighs]
[Olga] You child.
That's Sam-Sam's favorite.
Who's Sam?
Your boyfriend?
My father?
No!
Anyway, you shouldn't touch
my things here!
Where's my basket?
[suspicious music playing]
Um…
I threw it away.
I thought it was trash.
What?!
[tense music playing]
Oh, no! Why did you do that?!
[music intensifies]
From now on, you won't touch
any of my things here!
[in English] Okay?! Huh?!
I don't-- I don't even know
where my things are anymore!
You shouldn't have done that!
[pensive music playing]
You should've just left it messy!
Okay? You shouldn't have touched it!
You are unbelievable!
[dramatic music playing]
[gasping]
Oh my!
[Emerson exhales]
See?
[utensils clatter]
Oh, here… Here.
This is perfect. Oh, 'Toy, fish. Right?
What does the fish say,
and why does it go to the priest?
Go on.
[quirky music playing]
To… con-fish.
[chuckles]
The priest said, "Fish be with you."
It's still hot. Oh, milkfish!
Right?
What does the milkfish say
when it's about to die?
[Atoy] What?
[groans]
[in English] I'm daing.
[babbling, laughs]
Whoo! There you go.
Sorry, bro.
I know you're just trying
to make me laugh, but…
[sighs]
It's really hard
to fend off loneliness, isn't it?
[melancholic music playing]
Think about it. Just recently…
Ibyang was given to me.
Then, my family.
And now they're all gone.
They came quickly, but…
were taken from me just as fast.
[scoffs]
I'm fine.
[exhales, then clears throat]
I'm used to it.
I can handle being alone.
But why is it like that?
They made me feel happiness.
Then… [scoffs]
Just like that,
they're suddenly taken away.
You know, 'Toy…
you're not the only one
who feels that way.
[chuckles softly]
I feel that too, with Tonet.
Because, you know…
[giggles]
[sentimental music playing]
She was gone for so long.
Gone from my life, and…
when she came back, it didn't last.
It was so fast.
She was taken so quickly.
But you know…
every day…
Even if it's hard to accept…
I fight it off, but… I miss her, bro.
[Emerson chuckles softly]
I miss her, bro.
I miss my sister.
[melodramatic music playing]
[chuckles]
'Toy…
[bottles clink]
Bro, come on--
I'm fine.
Ah, you're making me sad. I'm fine.
It's hard, but I accept it. That's that.
[sniffs, then sighs]
You, what's your plan?
Life goes on.
[chuckles softly]
To moving forward in life.
[thuds]
[sniffs, then sighs]
[Emerson] Hey. [clears throat]
[Emerson] Boss.
Ah, well.
[pensive music playing]
If you're having a suit tailored,
just come back later.
The Master Cutter's chops have dropped.
He's a bit down in life.
Just come back, sir.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Captain Padua, this is
Lieutenant Gonzales reporting.
[in English] I was ordered
by Colonel Mercado to meet you
and deliver his directives.
[suspicious music playing]
Ah… [titters]
[Emerson] Cool.
You're connected
with Boss Mercado and Atoy?
[Emerson] Impressive!
[electronic blipping]
Emerson here, sir. Emerson Mendoza.
Sir, I need him cleared out.
[in English] Mission protocol.
Colonel Mercado will call soon.
No, no. Boss. [chuckles]
It's fine. No, it's fine--
He's with me. I'm part of Atoy's missions.
I'm his coworker.
And don't worry, sir.
I'm not a gossip. Ah, sir.
[in English] No, no, no. He's good.
He's good, he's good.
[in English] What is your name?
[in English] We are the Sokolov brothers.
[suspicious music playing]
[in Russian] Damn it!
[in English] Even the window cleaner.
[laptop blips]
[security guard, in English] We used AI
to see what he might look like.
[in English] The photos matched.
[in English] I want you
to find out everything about this man.
[in English] We tried, sir.
[in English] But unfortunately, no trace.
[in English] Then, we will find him.
[in English] I'm sure
he is looking for the decoder.
[electronic blipping]
The Master Cutter isn't here right now.
[Cita] He already has another assignment.
It's over! We have no hope!
Calm down. We'll try
to contact another tracker.
Huh? Who?
The… The child.
[Emerson] The child, child of a thread.
Hello, Atoy.
We found the suspect
in the five-million robbery.
I thought of something
we could profit from.
[Olga] That's a big amount of money.
How much are you selling this for?
[in English] It's already sold.
- [in English] Scam! Scammer!
- Mama?
[Mercado, in English] The laptop is locked
and requires a code.
Aside from the ambassador,
the only person who knows the code
is the head of IT at the embassy.
Your mission, get him.
UP NEXT
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias